## **AMOS GICHERO**

WEB DEVELOPER

Phone: (404) 519-3561 Email:

amosgichero@gmail.com GitHub:

https://github.com/gichero

Linkein: https:// www.linkedin.com/in/amos-

gichero-579913a4/

Website: www.amosgichero.com

Profile

I began my career as a software developer three years ago when I enrolled in a community college to study computer programming. Since graduating, I have enrolled in digitalCrafts an immersive coding bootcamp. I am passionate about technology and currently looking for opportunities in Atlanta. I have learned the following technologies in the past 3 years: Java, MySQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, PostgreSQL, Python, Node, Express, jQuery. I am currently learning React, and Redux.

Experience

## **Shaw industries**

2014-2017

Elutriation operator

Contributed to surpassing yearly records processing recycled carpet. I was consistently recognized for punctuality and working overtime.

Crete Carriers 2012-2014

Long haul truck driver

Accumulated over 150,000 miles without incidence delivering various goods nationally. Recognized as best rookie driver in 2013 for the Marietta, Georgia terminal.

## **Web Development Projects**

I have completed projects i using the Java, and JavaScript platforms. The projects can be viewed on my <u>portfolio</u>.

Education Digital crafts coding bootcamp

Buckhead, Atlanta 2017-2017

Chattahoochee technical college

Marietta, Georgia

Associates degree computer programming 2014-2016

University of Canberra Canberra, Australia

Bachelor business management 2002-2006